pcbcart.com 2013-08-18

# PCBCART - Professional China Prototype PCB Manufacturer - Help section

|   
---  
|    
|   Privacy statement  
---  
  
Our Privacy Statement is designed to assist you in understanding how we collect and use the personal information you provide to us and to assist you in making informed decisions when using our site and our products and   
services.

When you visit our Web site you may provide us with two types of information: personal information you   
knowingly choose to disclose that is collected on an individual basis and Web site use information collected   
as you and others browse our Web site.

**Personal Information**

    Once you make a purchase, request a catalog or other information, your name, shipping/mailing address,   
telephone number, email address and fax number are included in our customer file.

This information is used to ensure a quick, efficient flow of products and services to you.

This information may also be used for other purposes as outlined below.

**Postal Addresses**

Occasionally, PCBCART may make the names and addresses of our customer list available to carefully screened   
companies that offer products and/or services that may be of interest to you.

You may elect to opt out of either of these uses of your mailing address by contact us.

**Email Addresses**

Email addresses may be used to communicate information of interest to you about PCBCART. This includes Order   
Shipment/Tracking Information, Service Change Information or other PCBCART promotional emails. You may elect to opt out of any or all of these emails by contact us.

Emails may be sent by PCBCART or an authorized agent working for PCBCART. All authorized agents operate with a   
confidentiality agreement. Information sent in this manner will always include "opt out" options.

Email addresses are never rented, sold or traded to third parties.

**Notice of New Services and Changes**

Occasionally, we may also use the information we collect to notify you about important changes to our Web   
site, new services and special offers we think you will find valuable. As our customer, you will be given the opportunity to notify us of your desire not to receive these offers by sending us an email request

**Security of your Personal Information:**

We strictly protect the security of your personal information and carefully protect your data from loss,   
misuse, disclosure, alteration, destruction or unauthorized access. be kept strictly confidential and will not be sold, reused, rented, disclosed, or loaned. When you register with our website, PCBCART will not share your personal information with any third party.

**Web Site Use Information**

    Each time you visit our Web Site, our server automatically recognizes and logs your IP address. An IP address is basically the address of the computer making a request to our web server. No personal information or detail is obtained in this data interchange—a visitor's browser is not designed to provide this information.

During a Web site visit, we may ask a customer for contact information (email address, telephone number, fax number and addresses for shipping/billing). This information is collected on a voluntary basis—and only with customer approval.

**Cookies**

A cookie is a very small text document, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier. When you visit a Web site, that site's computer asks your computer for permission to store this file in a part of your hard   
drive specifically designated for cookies. Each Web site can send its own cookie to your browser if your   
browser's preferences allow it, but (to protect your privacy) your browser only permits a Web site to access the cookies it has already sent to you, not the cookies sent to you by other sites.

As you shop on our Web site, the site uses its cookies to differentiate you from other shoppers so your   
shopping cart is only available to you. In some cases, we also use cookies to prevent you from seeing   
unnecessary advertisements or requiring you to log in more than is necessary for security. Cookies do not   
allow us to gather any personal information about you and we do not generally store any personal information that you provided to us in your cookies.

**Contact Us**

If you have any questions or comments concerning our privacy statement please contact us.  

|  |
